Tang Zhiluo.
Do you know?
Before I met you,
I never trusted anyone.
You made me feel what love is.
You can't just walk away.
You can't leave me like this.
Do you hear me?
You can't leave me alone.
Your Highness, Miss Tang has arrived.
I am Tang Zhiluo.
Greetings, Prince Shuo.
Bring her up.
Your Highness, there is no need to test me.
I am indeed blind.
I am only blind,
not completely devoid of my senses.
Besides, when you wave your arm in front of me,
I can not only feel the air flow,
but also hear the wind.
Miss Tang, you are so young,
but my brother
said your medical skills are brilliant,
like Hua Tuo reborn.
I wonder if I have poor judgment,
or if the world is full of people fishing for fame
and bluffing.
Prince Yu, you flatter me.
I don't deserve it.
However, 'Hua Tuo reborn'
describes medical skills,
not age.
Otherwise, you could just find a turtle.
Wouldn't that be better?
We have never met before.
Why do you want to treat me?
A healer has a benevolent heart.
I can't bear to see patients suffer.
You are blind.
How can you see my suffering?
Your Highness suffers from headaches,
and I suffer from blindness.
As fellow patients,
I can naturally empathize with you.
In that case,
you may stay in my mansion.
Then I will trouble Your Highness.
Miss Tang, follow me.
Thank you.
What a hypocrite.
I want to see how long you can keep up this act.
When did Your Highness's headaches start?
Miss Tang, your medical skills are outstanding.
Can't you diagnose it?
I only know how to treat illnesses.
I don't tell fortunes.
Then what can Miss Tang diagnose?
Spleen deficiency and liver stagnation.
Phlegm and dampness clouding the upper body.
What does that mean?
You overthink too much.
And you are too suspicious.
Then, Miss Tang, can you cure it?
Of course I can.
Your Highness only needs one acupuncture session,
and a few doses of medicine.
Your condition should improve.
I think the acupuncture
can wait for another day.
What, is Your Highness afraid?
Fine, Your Highness can take the medicine first.
We'll talk about acupuncture another day.
As they say, it's hard to guard against villains.
Since Your Highness is still so childish,
it shows your condition isn't serious.
Just take your medicine on time.
Given time,
your condition should improve.
Then I shall take my leave.
Oh, my.
I didn't expect you to end up like this.
Shut up.
Miss Tang, let me do it.
It's not convenient for you.
It's not that I don't trust you, Miss Yunling.
But brewing medicine is also a doctor's duty.
Only by controlling the heat in real time
can the best effect be achieved.
Miss Tang, you are so good to His Highness.
Better than those imperial doctors from the palace.
Your Highness, please take your medicine.
How did you know it was me?
Right.
You are only blind.
You haven't lost all five senses.
You must have felt the flow of air, right?
It's the smell.
I only know how to treat people.
I don't treat plants.
I left the prescription on the stove.
Please brew and take it yourself, Your Highness.
Do not delay the treatment.
Miss Tang,
His Highness invites you to the lake to enjoy the water lanterns.
He specially asked Yunling to bring you some clothes.
Enjoy the water lanterns?
I understand.
Please tell His Highness
that I will definitely be there.
I humiliated her so much.
Will she come,
or leave in anger?
Your Highness.
Miss Tang, you're here.
Please have a seat.
I'm sorry.
I just felt that this ribbon
didn't quite match
your outfit.
It's fine.
As long as I didn't scare Your Highness.
I originally thought your eyes
were blind from birth.
I was wondering where you learned your medical skills.
Little did I know...
Half a year ago, I went up the mountain to gather herbs
and accidentally fell off a cliff.
Not only did I lose all my memories,
but my eyes were also pierced by thorns.
My royal brother said
your medical skills are excellent.
Can't you cure your own eyes?
A doctor can hardly treat herself.
Your Highness invited me to enjoy the lanterns.
Where are they?
Are you naturally incapable of getting angry,
or are you just too good at pretending?
How could I not be angry?
Your Highness teased me during the day,
and I called you a despicable person.
Have you forgotten so quickly?
It's just that you wanted to humiliate me,
and I don't care.
A doctor treats both the body and the mind.
If Your Highness can cooperate with the treatment because of this,
why wouldn't I do it?
It was my fault.
I apologize to you.
How about
I promise you one condition?
Then Your Highness should cooperate with the treatment.
Except for that.
Then Your Highness can count the river lanterns for me.
Count the lanterns?
Is that not okay either?
Then,
I'll count the lanterns.
Follow me.
We're here.
I'll count the lanterns, and you walk forward.
One.
Two.
Three.
I want to see if you're faking it.
Four.
Could it be
that she really can't see?